Preliminary Guide to the John A. Wilson papers, 1974-1993 MS2190
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
John A. Wilson papers
1974-1993
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
MS2190
105 Linear Feet
This collection consists of the office files of Council of the District of Columbia Member John A. Wilson.
Oversize-folder UP0042
Oversize-folder UP0041
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Gift of Bonnie Brio Wilson 1993.
Conditions Governing Access note
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical note
John A. Wilson (1943-1993) served as a member of the Council of the District of Columbia from 1974 until 1993. He had represented Ward 2 for 16 years before winning the chairman's seat in 1990. He was known for his knowledge of the city's budget and influence over the city's finances. Prior to his work in the D.C. Government, Wilson had been a civil rights activist as an early organizer and later vice chairman of the Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee. In 1969, Wilson became the legislative director for the National Sharecropper's Fund, an advocacy group for migrant farm workers. He helped run its Washington office for six years. In 1971, Wilson served as co-chairman for the campaign for Walter Fauntroy for D.C.'s delegate to Congress.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of correspondence, constituent records, publications, statements, photographs, negatives, slides, newspaper clippings, and audio cassettes. The material dates from 1974-93. These files are from Wilson's office during his time as a member of the District of Columbia Council. These files cover a wide range of topics of interest to Mr. Wilson during his time in office. The subjects include among others urban renewal, healthcare, campaign data, historic preservation, and transportation. Although they were separated into series in the finding aid, the folders were not rearranged and all original folder titles were maintained. Therefore, this collection may take longer to use for research as more boxes will have to be explored to ensure finding all relevant documents.
Arrangement note
Collection remains in original order, but folder titles were alphabetized within the finding aid and three series were created for ease of browsing the finding aid: Campaigns and elections; Correspondence; and Subject files.
AIDS (Disease); Homelessness -- Washington (D.C.); Washington (D.C.) Politics and government; Transportation -- Washington Metropolitan Area; Urban renewal; City council members -- Washington (D.C.); District of Columbia. City Council.; Wilson, John A.
- Campaigns and elections, 1974-1993; Series 1
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of correspondence, financial records, campaign literature, lists of individuals, schedules, and election results documenting John A. Wilson's political career. The material dates from 1974 to 1993.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically in this finding aid, but the physical files in their boxes are not.
  - Campaign, 1980; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Campaign, 1984; Series 1 (Box 37B, Folder 13)
  - Campaign - Bills to be paid, 1980; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Campaign - fundraiser, 1980 June 22; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Campaign - Gray fundraiser returns, 1980; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Campaign - Hughes challenge, 1980; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Campaign - Misc, undated; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Campaign - Misc, 1988; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Campaign - nurses questionnaire, 1980; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Campaign - Peter Hart, 1980; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Campaign - Retired citizens/teachers questionnaire, 1980; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Campaign - Treasurer's vouchers, 1980; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Campaign artwork, 1988; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Campaign bank documents, 1976; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Campaign booklet, 1984; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Campaign brochure, 1980; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Campaign budget, 1988; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Campaign buttons and bumper stickers, undated; Series 1 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    The buttons in the clear bag and the bumper stickers came to the archive in 2018 as part of the donation from Bonnie Wilson. Acc 2018.050.
  - Campaign checks, undated; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Campaign Contribution records, 1980; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Campaign copies and receipts, 1980; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Campaign correspondence, undated; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Campaign finance reports, undated; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Campaign finance reports, 1984; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Campaign financial materials, 1980; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Campaign financial reports, undated; Series 1 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Campaign forums, 1988 and undated; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    General
    folder contains the undated document titled Platform questions for mayoral and Ward 2 council candidates. This documnt is from the donation from Bonnie Wilson, December 7, 2018 (accession 2018.050)
  - Campaign info, 1980; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Campaign lists, 1982; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Campaign lists, undated; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Campaign literature, undated; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Campaign materials, 1988; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Campaign materials, undated; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Campaign Office Lease, undated; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Campaign Opening, 1988; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Campaign openings, 1984; Series 1 (Box 37B, Folder 7)
  - Campaign opposition, 1988; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Campaign paraphernalia, undated; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Campaign paraphernalia, undated; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Campaign paraphernalia, undated; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Campaign poll, undated; Series 1 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Campaign reading file, 1988; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Campaign report, 1988 June 10; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Campaign report, 1988 August 10; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Campaign report, 1988 October 10; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Campaign report, 1988 December 10; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Campaign report, 1989 January 31; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Campaign report, 1984; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Campaign report, 1982 June 10; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Campaign report, 1984 October; Series 1 (Box 37A, Folder 24)
  - Campaign schedule, undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Campaign schedule, undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Campaign schedule, 1988; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Campaign schedule, 1980; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Campaign steering committee, 1980; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Campaign vouchers, 1988 March 10; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Campaign vouchers, undated; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Candidate financial reports, undated; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Candidate list, 1992 May; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Contribution letters, undated; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Contributions, 1976 March 30; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Contributions A-L, 1980; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Contributions M-Z, 1980; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Election - contribution cards, 1980; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Election - finances, 1980; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Election brochures, undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Election of Officers, 1992 June 04; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Election Reform Postponement, 1982 March 29; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Election results, undated; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Election results - at-large special election, 1977 July 17; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Election results - Board of Education, 1977 November 8; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Election results - council primary, 1988; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Election results - DC council primary, 1976 September; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Election results - DC primary, 1976 May; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Election results - DC primary, 1976 May; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Election results - general, 1986 November 04; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Election results - general, 1984 November 06; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Election results - general, 1981 November 03; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Election results - general, 1979 November 06; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Election results - general, 1976 November 01; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Election results - primary, 1978 September 12; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Election results - special election, 1979 May 01; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Elections, undated; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Elections, undated; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Elections - petitions, 1984 September; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Fundraiser, 1976 August 03; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Fundraiser, 1976 August 24; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Fundraiser, 1983 July 13; Series 1 (Box 37A, Folder 20)
  - Fundraiser, 1982 October 28; Series 1 (Box 37A, Folder 21)
  - Fundraiser - Berens/Mizzer breakfast, 1988 May 26; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Fundraiser - Bonderman's, undated; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Fundraiser - breakfast, 1987 October 19; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Fundraiser - Bristol Hotel, 1985 July 01; Series 1 (Box 37A, Folder 6)
  - Fundraiser - investment bankers, 1987 December; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Fundraiser - parking execs, 1988 April 27; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Fundraiser - Peeble's House, 1988 June 01; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Fundraiser at the Dakota, 1987 September 29; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Fundraising, 1980; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Fundraising, undated; Series 1 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Fundraising lists, undated; Series 1 (Box 37B, Folder 15)
  - General Election, 1988 November 01; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - General Election, 1988; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - General Election, 1988; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - General election literature, 1988, undated; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - General election returns, 1988; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Master contributor list, 1988-1989; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Mayoral campaign, 1982; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Mayoral campaign, 1982; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Mayoral campaign - bank statements, 1982; Series 1 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Mayoral campaign - contribution letters, 1982; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Mayoral campaign - copies of checks, 1982; Series 1 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Mayoral campaign - fundraising lists/business community, 1982; Series 1 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Mayoral campaign - Miscellaneous, 1982; Series 1 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Mayoral campaign - Rothstein and Buckley, 1982; Series 1 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Mayoral campaign - thank you letters, 1982; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Mayoral campaign letters, 1982; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Mayoral race, 1986; Series 1 (Box 37A, Folder 19)
  - Mayoral race, undated; Series 1 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Mayoral race - chron file, 1982; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Mayoral race - office lease, 1982; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Mayoral race - O'Neal party, 1982 March 24; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Mayoral race - phone bank, 1982; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Mayoral race - phone bank procedures, 1982; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Mayoral race - releases and correspondence, 1982; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Mayoral race - thank you letters, 1982; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Mayoral race - Webster party, 1982 April 1; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Misc. contribution records, undated; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Petty cash receipts - reelection, 1988; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Phone bank, 1988; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Primary Election Day, 1988; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Primary literature, 1988 September 13; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Primary results, 1984; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Primary results, 1988 May 03; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Primary returns, 1984; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Primary/General Election, 1984; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Reelection, undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Reelection, 1992; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Re-election, 1980; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Re-election - announcement, 1984; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Re-election - bills to be paid, 1976; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Re-election - C.G. mailing lists, undated; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 39)
  - Re-election - campaign correspondence, 1976; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Re-election - campaign invitations, undated; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Re-election - correspondence, 1984; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Re-election - endorsements, 1984; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Re-election - FAIR Tony Mizzer, 1984; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Re-election - flyers, 1984; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Re-election - general contribution, 1976; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Re-election - mailing lists, undated; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 38)
  - Re-election - office lease, 1984; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Re-election - phone bank, undated; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 35)
  - Re-election - poll coverage, 1984; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 36)
  - Re-election - poll coverage, 1984 November; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 37)
  - Re-election - results, 1984; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 33)
  - Re-election - returned mailings, 1984; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Re-election - telephone procedures, 1984; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 34)
  - Re-election - thank you letters, 1976; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Re-election - thank you letters, 1984; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - Re-election - various mailing lists, undated; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - Re-election campaign, 1988; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Re-election campaign, 1984; Series 1 (Box 37B, Folder 6)
  - Re-election campaign - Treasurer/Chairman records, 1988; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Re-election committee, undated; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Re-election literature, 1980; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Re-election Misc., 1984; Series 1 (Box 37B, Folder 14)
  - Re-election volunteers, undated; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Wilson campaign, undated; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Wilson campaign, undated; Series 1 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Wilson for Chairman, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Wilson for Chairman - Anton's Responses, undated; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Wilson for Chairman - Artwork, undated; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Wilson for Chairman - Bulk rate, undated; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Wilson for Chairman - Campaign clippings, undated; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Wilson for Chairman - Contribution cards and letters, 1989 July 31; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Wilson for Chairman - Contributor list, undated; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Wilson for Chairman - Copies of checks, 1990 January 31; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Wilson for Chairman - Copies of checks, 1989 July 31; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Wilson for Chairman - Dear friend letters, undated; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Wilson for Chairman - Fenn and King Contract, undated; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Wilson for Chairman - Finance committee, undated; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Wilson for Chairman - Hatch Act, undated; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Wilson for Chairman - Information for brochure, undated; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Wilson for Chairman - Invitation list, undated; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Wilson for Chairman - Misc., 1990; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Wilson for Chairman - Official filings, undated; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Wilson for Chairman - Other candidates, undated; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Wilson for Chairman - Vouchers for checks, undated; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Wilson for City Council, undated; Series 1 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Wilson for National Committeeman, undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, 1969-1993; Series 2
  This series contains incoming and some outgoing correspondence from the office of John A. Wilson. It dates from 1969 to 1993.
  - AIDS Correspondence, undated; Series 2 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - AIDS Correspondence, undated; Series 2 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Condolence letters, undated; Series 2 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Constituent correspondence, 1992-1993; Series 2 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1973-1981; Series 2 (Box 67B, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, undated; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1986 January; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1986 January; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1986 March; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1986 April; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1986 May; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1986 June; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1986 July; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1986 August; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1986 September; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1986 October; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1986 November; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1986 December; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, undated; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, 1985; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, 1985; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, 1984 January; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1984 January; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1984 March; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1984 April; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1984 May; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1984 June; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1984 July; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1984 August; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1984 September; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1984 October; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1984 November; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1984 December; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1985 January; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1985 January; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1985 March; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1985 April; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1985 May; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1985 June; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1985 November; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1989 January; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1989 January; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1989 March; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1989 April; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1989 May; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1989 June; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1989 July; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1989 August; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1989 September; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1989 October; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1989 November; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1989 December; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1990 January; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1990 January; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1990 March; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1990 April; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1990 May; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1990 June; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1990 July; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1990 August; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1990 September; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1990 October; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1990 November; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1990 December; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1980; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, undated; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence [1 of 2], 1983-1992; Series 2 (Box 67B, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence [2 of 2], 1983-1992; Series 2 (Box 67B, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Legislative, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence -- sympathy letters, 1993; Series 2 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence -- sympathy letters, 1993; Series 2 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence -- sympathy letters, 1993; Series 2 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence -- sympathy letters, 1993; Series 2 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence -- sympathy letters, 1993; Series 2 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence -- sympathy letters, 1993; Series 2 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence -- sympathy letters, 1993; Series 2 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence -- sympathy letters, 1993; Series 2 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence -- sympathy letters, 1993; Series 2 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence -- sympathy letters, 1993; Series 2 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence -- sympathy letters, 1993; Series 2 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence -- sympathy letters, 1993; Series 2 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence -- sympathy letters, 1993; Series 2 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence -- sympathy letters, 1993; Series 2 (Box 67B, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence -- sympathy letters, 1993; Series 2 (Box 67B, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence -- sympathy letter from President Clinton, 1993; Series 2 (Box 67B, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, undated; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - General correspondence, 1980; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - General correspondence, 1981; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - General correspondence, 1978; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - JAW Personal Correspondence, 1974-1978; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - JAW Personal Correspondence, 1979-1980; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Letters, undated; Series 2 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Letters - breakfast, 1988 June 14; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Letters and position papers, undated; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Letters to the editor, undated; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Letters to the Mayor, undated; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Misc. Correspondence, undated; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Misc. correspondence, undated; Series 2 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Misc. letters, undated; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Thank you letter - General Election Day and Phone Bank Work, 1988; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Thank you letter for signing petition, 1988; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Thank you letters, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Thank you letters, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Thank you letters, 1980; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Thank you letters, 1980; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Thank you letters, 1980; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Thank you letters, 1980; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Thank you letters, undated; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Thank you letters - incoming, 1987; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Thank you letters - Primary Day, 1988; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Zoning correspondence, undated; Series 2 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Zoning correspondence, undated; Series 2 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Zoning correspondence, undated; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 2)